[{"answer": "Never have sex with the clientele", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Always get a tip", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yes, you can", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Oh night shift", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Great", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Fifty bucks", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You're shirking your duties for this Nazi. For that you pay a price, and the price is fifty bucks", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yeah, but what you're doin' to me ain't fair. And, you are completely and totally taking advantage of me and your position. So fifty bucks is the perfect price", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Because I said so", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You can't watch TV because the noise will interfere with our ritual", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Your sweet side", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You get whatever you want. And you know what else I love about you", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " If this is gonna be like one of those afterbirth conversations, I don't think I wanna hear this", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You swallowed what", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Right. 404", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " What do we need", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " What do we need", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Ice", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Ice", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Ice", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Ice", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Ice", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Ice", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yeah. Ice", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What do you expect, my friend, a fuckin' floor show", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't know. Do you", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "For fucking what", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "\"That I said you might have been unfaithful", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Are you condescending to me, my friend", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Why don't you just say it", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Absolutely not, I would never do that", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Say what", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You think you're superior to me, don't ya, my friend? You don't think I notice there is a gag in the woman's mouth", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Naturally", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Forget it, listen to me. There's a gun in my suitcase behind the bed, it's loaded..", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Fine. Get the gun and I'll shoot", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "There are two sides to a plate, still you only eat off of one. Now GET THE GUN", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I'm a werewolf, my friend! Get the gun", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Put it this way, God made up for what he did to Gumby with my friend here", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Show him your cock, my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What was what like", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Oh, for fuck sake, my friend, what do you want me to say", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "If I ever saw her again, I'd run the other way", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "If I ever saw her again, I'd run the other way", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I promise", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Three's good", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Check up on 'em", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "No, not at all. It's New Year's Eve and I'm here alone. If there was somebody else here, no problem, but I'm by myself. And looking after your kids is a pain in the ass I don't need", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "-- No, they're not a pain in the ass, it's the situation that's a pain in the ass", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "my friend, go to sleep", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "You washed off the ointment", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Who", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Gotcha, my friend from work", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Tell 'em Teddy from work's on the phone, and it's a major fuckin' emergency", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Not my friend from work, I'm calling my friend! I'm Teddy. Just say my friend", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Not my friend from work, I'm calling my friend! I'm Teddy. Just say my friend", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": " No my friend, this hasn't been my best New Year. This year's starting off pretty badly", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "What's the problem", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Sounds to me like a pretty great way to start off the night", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Sounds to me like a pretty great way to start off the night", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "-- Skipping over the witches", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "So, later, in another room, some crazy sucking maniac sticks a gun in my face and forces me to play out some psychosexual drama with his wife", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "No, he didn't make me fuck his wife, he thought I'd fucked his wife! He held me at gunpoint with a loaded gun", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "I don't know, I'm not a gun guy. It was big", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Yeah, something like that", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Hold on.  Anybody live here named...  What's her name again", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "You're my friend", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "I'm my friend  And this is my friend", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Having a drink", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Are you kidding, he'll be asleep till Christmas", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "No, not thank you. Whadya say about the tasty beverage", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "Fuckin' good, my friend. It's fuckin' good. Let's try it again, shall we? So, my friend, whadya think about the beverage", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "It's good", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "It's fuckin' good", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "Look, guys, you paid for the room. As long as you don't break up the furniture, you can do whatever the fuck you want. And me personally, I don't care if you break up the furniture. You don't have to explain anything to me. Whatever constitutes a good time as far as you guys are concerned is your business", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "Take part in what", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "my friend, you ready", "docId": "Four-Rooms.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "my friend, you ready", "qsentId": 80}]